Juho Bai

Deep Learning Scientist

Sogang Univ. Seoul, Korea

☑ juho@sogang.ac.kr

□ 010-2047-8285

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a creative and enthusiastic Deep learning scientist with over ten years of experience in the IT field. I have experience designing and carrying out computing experiments, data analysis, researching related works, and writing technical proposals. I possess excellent analytical and communications skills and a dedicated approach to working in a highly expertized environment. I am currently looking for a challenging opportunity within the new domain.

EDUCATION

Ph.D in Computer Science and Engineering, Sogang Univ

Aug 2021

MS in Computer Science and Engineering, Sogang Univ

Aug 2011

BS in Computer Science and Engineering, Sogang Univ

Aug 2009

PUBLICATIONS

- o Juho Bai. Deep learning methods using expert domain knowledge for similar search of patent documents. Sogang Univ, 2021 (phd thesis)
- Juho Bai, Inwook Shim, and Seog Park. Pai-net:similar patent search network using prior art information. IEEE Access, 2021 (SCIE), under review
- Juho Bai, Inwook Shim, and Seog Park. Mexn: Multi-stage extraction network for patent document classification. Applied Sciences, 10(18):6229, 2020 (SCIE)
- o Juho Bai and Seog Park. Lexai: Legal document similarity analysis service using explainable ai. Journal of KIISE, 47(11):1061–1070, 2020 (KCI)
- Juho Bai and Yeji Kim. Environmental forecasting service server and method using location and surrounding environmental information, Korea Patent 10-2020-0021800, Feb. 2021 (Patent)
- o Juho Bai, Sehwa Park, and Seog Park. The method of semantic information indexing for spatiotemporal database searching system, Korea Patent 10-2016-0009215, Jan. 2016 (Patent)

SKILLS

- o C, C++, C#, Python, pyTorch, Tensorflow
- o MSSQL, MariaDB, Oracle, Embedded Control Systems, IOT sensor data processing

PROJECTS

A Development of Deid based on Differential privacy

Mar 2019 - Dec 2019

o 차분 프라이버시 기반 비식별화 기술 개발// 정보통신기획평가원//Research assistant

Design and implementation system of spatio-temporal archive

Dec 2014 - Nov 2015

o 시공간 아카이브의 설계 및 시스템 구현// 사단법인 한국산학연합회//Research assistant

Access control for web app version management

Jul 2014 - Jun 2015

o 다중 웹 앱 버전 관리를 위한 보안 접근제어// 서강대학교//Research assistant

Design and build Sensing Data as a Secure, Reliable Service

Jun 2014 - Mar 2014

o 안전하고 신뢰할 수 있는 서비스로서의 센싱데이터 설계 및 구축// (재) 한국연구재단//Research assistant

Training Team for CFTR for the Utilization of Big Data

Sep 2013 - Feb 2014

o 빅데이터 활용을 위한 창의적 기반기술 연구인력 양성팀// (재) 한국연구재단//Research assistant

Design and implementation of web tools using Lego modeling

Jan 2013 - Jun 2013

o 레고 모델링 기법을 이용한 웹 앱 개발툴의 설계 및 구현// 엘지전자(주)//Research assistant

EBPP system for an integrated smartphone environment

Oct 2012 - Sep 2013

o 스마트폰 통합 결제 시스템 구축을 위한 전자고지결제// 한국산업기술평가관리원//Research assistant

Requirements and Quality Validation TD for Convergence SW

Jul 2012 - Dec 2012

o 융합 소프트웨어를 위한 요구 및 품질검증 서비스 개발// 정보통신산업진흥원//Research assistant

Seoul Accord

Jul 2011 - Feb 2012

o 서울 어코드 활성화 사업// 서강대학교//Research assistant

Training for a Healthcare system based on Pervasive computing

Mar 2008 - Feb 2013

o Pervasive 컴퓨팅 기반의 의료 시스템을 위한 핵심 S/W 인력 양성 사업팀// (재) 한국연구재단//RA

WORK EXPERIENCE

Galactic Entertainment inc.

Seoul, Korea

Co-founder, CTO

Aug 2018 - Present

o Design deep learning-based translation memory system

Y&J Partners

Seoul, Korea

Chief Technology Officer

Aug 2019 - Aug 2020

o Design environmental data prediction using geo-spatial dataset and deep learning R&D for legal tech

Inha Technical College

Incheon, Korea

Adjunct Faculty

Mar 2013 - Dec 2013

o Lecture database schema design and implementation(spring), data structures and algorithms(autumn)